<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Cybonito 2015</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Drawer Opened</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Drawer Closed</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string-array name="coding" >
    <item>

 It is an online coding event on the lines of Google Code Jam.
The Event constitutes of two rounds, namely:
1.	Qualification Round:
2.	On site Final round:
Website :  www.srmcodejam.co.in
Qualification round starts on Friday 20th Feb at 5:30 pm.
    </item>

    <item>

With the Cybonito 2k15 comes again the Blind Coding with its fourth version as Blind
Coding V 4.0. This time it is even more bigger and better with a whole new bunch of phases.
The tech scholars will have to pass through the various phases to reach the final phase and
compete there with the one of the finest geeks.
The various phases will be as follows:

	SCREENING QUIZ
	ERROR SEARCH
	BLIND CODING


    </item>

    </string-array>





    <string-array name="fun">

        <item>Details will be uploaded soon.</item>
        <item>Details will be uploaded soon.</item>
        <item>Slashcounts , strike lines and announce a full house.
Cybonito welcomes you to the all time fun event – TAMBOLA.
</item>
        <item>
To participate in this event a team should consist of 3 members only.
This event will consist of 3 rounds.

•	Round 1
Two teams will complete with each other. They will have 1.5 minutes each to enact the movie which
is given to them randomly. One member will act and other will have to guess. The team which succeeds
first will qualify for round 3.The other one will be eliminated.

•	Round 2
One team member will be given an audio. He or she will have to guess the movie related to audio and
enact it. The other team members will have to guess . They will be given 2 minutes for this round .
Top 10 teams having minimum time taken will qualify for the round 3(the final round).

•	Round 3
This is the final round.One of the team members will be given a movie which they can only draw
on board and others have to guess the movie. Total time given in this is 2 minutes. The team which takes minimum
time will be crowned the winner.
</item>

        <item>Details will be uploaded soon.</item>
        <item>Details will be uploaded soon.</item>
        <item>Details will be uploaded soon.</item>
<item>
Type Pixit is a fun event played in 2 beats.
The first beat challenges your peerless speed of typing and if you resonate with beat , the 2nd beat veils a
note for you to play and prizes.

</item>
    </string-array>



    <string-array name="toolsandhardware">

        <item>1)Venue :: M.Tech Lab  2)Time:: 10.30-12.00 on 2nd day.</item>
        <item>1)Venue :: Lab3  2)Time:: 2-3.30 on 1st day.</item>
        <item>Details will be updated soon.</item>

    </string-array>




    <string-array name="game">

        <item>Games like: 1)	Counter Strike 1.6 2)	Fifa  3)	NFS </item>
        <item>Games like: 1)	Mario 1.6 2)	Contra  3)	Pacman   4)Tanks </item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="visuals">

        <item>

Time limit of clip : 3-‐5 minutes
•	1 to 4 members per team.
•	Original, fresh ideas will be given more preference and will fetch you more marks
•	Teams should make sure that the feelings of the characters are conveyed through the dialogues too and not music alone
•	Innovation in story-­‐telling approach, filming or in any aspect of film-­‐making would be welcome
•	The teams to bring along the final video clip along with the RAW files in a pendrive.
•	The participants should expect cross-questioning
•	Participants are allowed to use any software they find convenient
•	If the footage used is not original, proper credits to the owner/source should be given.
•	The teams have to make the movie on any 1 of the following topics:
	Hope : picture abhi baaki hai mere dost
	Mother: mere paas maa hai
	Women Safety: basanti in kutton ke saamne mat naachna

        </item>
        <item>
Guidelines:   Profile the campus!
This competition will take you on a chase across the campus of SRM University. Participants are required to recreate the
exact copy of a set of images provided to them on the spot. The images will be from within the campus.
Find the spots, get there quickly and match the pictures given to you. The exactness is measured by the following aspects
of the image:
•	Angle of click
•	Framing
•	Focus
•	Exposure
Find the exact angle, exact frame and exact magnification! Test your photography and scavenging skills!
•	On the spot event
•	Time limit: 3 hours
•	Only 1 participant per team.
</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="quiz">

        <item>

            The Event contain two rounds.
            •	Round 1
            Any random word or the name of a thing will be given to the contestant )in pair of two) .
            They had to complete with another contestant and guess the word more earlier than other.
            Remember you can’t say anything you have to use the power of drawing to make your companion
            understand what you are trying to say. The team which guesses the word earlier qualifies for next round.
            •	Round 2
            A couple of pictures will be shown to the qualifying team continuously .
            After the gap of 5 sec, they have to write the name of the things shown in the picture in
            sequence they are shown.
            Then teams with less number of marks are eliminated and the no. of pictures are increased
            and the game is played again.
            Till we get out top three winners.

        </item>


 <item>An opportunity to lay your hands on some good amount of cash by just-contesting  the brilliance of your observation skills.
All you have to do is, simply  identify the logo from the pool of unique logo types. Shine for 2 bouts and enjoy the perks.
</item>
        <item>
After a great success in Cybonito 2014, we are back with the next version of CyboTech.
CyboTech v2 would comprise of 3 rounds. Each round would comprise of questions, a tech savvy would like to solve and answer.
Each round would help us to find the best out of the best TechGurus attending the Cybonito this year.

•	Round 1
The first round is an online quiz. It will be conducted using a software in which the contestants will have to solve 40 questions within a time span of 15 minutes.
The quiz will consist of:
20 questions from the geek world
20 questions from the code world
The top ten contestants will qualify for the next round.

•	Round 2
The next round is a combination of a crossword puzzle and multiple choice questions aimed at
testing the mental abilities of the contestants. Some MCQ based questions will be flashed on the
screen for a short duration of time and simultaneously the contestants will have to solve some
questions with the help of audio and visual clues. The top four contestants will move on for the final round.

•	Round 3
The third and final round is a programming based round. The contestants will be given some
problems in either C, C++ or Java as the contestants want. There will be three questions
one each for coding, debugging and finding the output. The first person to solve the three
problems will be awarded the winner!
</item>

    </string-array>

    <string name="department">Computer Science The Department of Computer Science is renowned
        for cutting edge research and for imparting state of the art world class education.
        We attract some of the excellent students and faculty. The Department of Computer Science imparts
        international level training and research. The Department provides high standard computing
        facilities to the students. It also promotes active industry-department affiliation by
        finding common areas of interest and taking part in research projects and consultancy services.
        Our research exists in the areas of systems, software, networking, databases, security,
        and foundations of computer science, artificial intelligence, robotics, and scientific computing.
        Besides basic research, interdisciplinary work on applications that stimulate basic research has
        been undertaken under Department of Computer Science.</string>

    <string name="cybonito">The need for efficient and accurate calculation and automation has over
        the years resulted in the birth of a new science. What started as a simple calculating device became
        a phenomenon that changed the face of technology, business and governance.Computer Science has
        revolutionized our lifestyle.The Computer Science and engineering department of SRM University,
        NCRCampus brings you a plethora of events ranging from hardcore programming contests, nerve wracking
        puzzles and games enriching workshops and presentations.</string>






</resources>